Hello everyone, how are you all? My name is
Kashyap Sharma. I recently
registered a claim for my vehicle with ICICI Lord, and that claim was
successfully passed. So, I want to
share this experience with you so that
you too have the
convenience of this thing and you know how to
register a claim quickly with ICICI insurance and achieve it successfully.
So this is an application
of ICICI group. Here you have to
type 'hi' and the robot will communicate with you.
And then you have to go
to all these options -
All About Terms.
As you can see, you will get all the
information in it and you
can select your vehicle and process the claim.
After this, you will get a call from the agency,
and the entire procedure will be through ICICI Lord
only. My experience with the
claim has been very good, and I
hope your experience is also good. So I would always
Suggest to go for ICICI
Lord for Vehicle Insurance Thank You